Julia: So who’s that with you?
Sarah: It’s Anna, you know, the intelligent girl.
Julia: Anna, wow! She’s very different.
Her hair’s blonde.
Sarah: Yes, and she doesn’t wear glasses now.
Julia: What does she do?
Sarah: She’s a journalist.
She works for a newspaper – The Times, I think.
Julia: Is she good?
Sarah: I don’t know. I don’t read The Times.
Julia: And who’s that?
The man with grey hair.
Sarah: It’s Matt! Remember?
Julia: Matt! No!
What does he do?
Sarah: He’s a teacher. He teaches French.
Julia: Where does he work?
Sarah: At our old school.
Julia: At our old school? How sad!
Sarah: Yes, and he’s married to Laura.
Julia: Laura?
From our class? Really?
Sarah: Yes!
Julia: Is that her?
Sarah: Yes.
That’s her, with Matt!
Julia: Very ugly shoes.
Sarah: Yes, horrible.
Laura: Sarah, hi!
Great to see you again!
Sarah: Laura?
Laura: Oh, and Julia.
Julia: Yes, er …
Hi, Laura. Great photos.
Laura: What? Oh, yes.
Good party.
Julia: I love your shoes.
They’re beautiful.